BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing (Metal, Machinery, Computer and Electronic, Electrical, Transportation Equipment, Furniture, Miscellaneous)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1937-1939 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1938-1940 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1925-1940 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1938-1940 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1939-1940 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1936-1937 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1937-1938 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1938-1939 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1938-1940 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Broom and Whisk Makers' Union, 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (furniture), 1936-1939 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (furniture), 1936-1939 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (furniture), 1938-1940 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (furniture), 1939-1940 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (furniture), 1939-1940 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (furniture), 1938-1940 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (furniture), 1938-1940 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Carpenters and Joiners (furniture) (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Die Casting Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Die Casting Workers, CIO, 1938-1940 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (manufacturing), 1934-1939 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (manufacturing), 1938-1939 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (manufacturing), 1939-1940 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (manufacturing), 1937-1940 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (manufacturing), 1937-1941 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (manufacturing), 1941-1943 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Operating Engineers (metal, electronics, and furniture manufacturing), 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Firemen and Oilers (train, metal, and brush manufacturing), 1937-1943 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Foremen's Association of America, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1937-1939 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1935-1939 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1938-1939 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1938-1940 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - United Furniture Workers, CIO, 1939-1940 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1936-1938 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1935-1938 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1936-1939 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1936-1939 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1937-1939 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1937-1940 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (clock and watch manufacturing), 1937-1940 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (cutlery manufacturing), 1938-1941 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    United Cutlery Workers of America; some agreements marked as confidential
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (dental instruments manufacturing), 1937-1939 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (furniture manufacturing), 1937-1940 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (metal, machinery, tool, and appliance manufacturing), 1937-1940 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (optical workers), 1937-1940 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    United Optical Workers Union
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (toy manufacturing), 1937-1940 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Machinists, AFL (metal and, machinery manufacturing), 1937 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Machinists, AFL (metal and, machinery manufacturing), 1935-1938 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Machinists, AFL (metal and, machinery manufacturing), 1937-1939 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Machinists, AFL (metal and, machinery manufacturing), 1938-1939 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Machinists, AFL (metal and, machinery manufacturing), 1930-1940 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Machinists, AFL (metal and, machinery manufacturing), 1939-1940 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Machinists, AFL (metal and, machinery manufacturing), 1939-1940 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Mechanics Educational Society, 1935-1938 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Mechanics Educational Society, 1938-1949 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Mechanics Educational Society, 1939-1940 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Mechanics Educational Society, 1939-1940 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Mechanics Educational Society, 1939-1940 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Metal Engravers, 1937 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    Contains no agreements, only notes from Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - Metal Polishers, AFL, 1937-1938 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Metal Polishers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Metal Polishers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Metal Polishers, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Metal Polishers, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Metal Polishers, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Metal Trades Council, AFL, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Metal Trades Council, AFL, 1938-1939 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Metal Trades Council, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Metal Trades Council, AFL, 1940 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Metal Trades Council, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Metal Trades Council, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Metal Trades Council, AFL, 1940-1941 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers (smelting and metal manufacturing), 1935-1939 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers (smelting and metal manufacturing), 1937-1939 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers (smelting and metal manufacturing), 1937-1940 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - United Mine Workers (metal, machinery, furniture, and candle manufacturing), 1937-1940 (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - Molders, AFL, 1935-1939 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Molders, AFL, 1928-1939 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Molders, AFL, 1938-1939 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Molders, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Molders, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Molders, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Molders, AFL, 1937-1940 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Molders, AFL, 1937-1940 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Molders, AFL, 1938-1940 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Molders, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Molders, AFL, 1939-1940 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Molders, AFL, 1937-1940 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America - NY, NJ, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1937-1938 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1935-1939 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1937-1938 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1937-1939 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1938-1941 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1938-1940 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1939-1940 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1939-1940 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1937-1938 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1939-1940 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1938-1940 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1937-1940 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1938-1940 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1940 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1940 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1940 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Battery Workers' Union
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1940 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1940 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1939-1940 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    Formerly b74f11
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1930-1936 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1936-1939 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1937-1940 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1941 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1940-1941 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1940-1941 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1937-1941 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1938-1941 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1938-1941 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Metal Trades Workers, AFL, Florida, 1940-1941 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1938-1941 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1939-1941 (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1940-1941 (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1941-1942 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1939-1942 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1940-1942 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1939-1942 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Boiler Makers, Iron Ship Builders, and Helpers, 1936-1937 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Marine and Shipbuilding Workers, Maryland, 1939-1940 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Marine and Shipbuilding Workers, Pennsylvania, 1939 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    Iron, Steel and Tin Workers
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1936-1938 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1937-1939 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1937-1939 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1937-1940 (Box 78, Folder 22)
    Iron, Steel and Tin Workers, Formerly Confidential
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, CIO, 1936-1939 (Box 78, Folder 23)
    Iron, Steel and Tin Workers; some agreements marked as confidential
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1936-1939 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1937-1940 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, 1936-1938 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Maybury Shoe Company Workers, NH, 1938-1940 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Suit Case, Bag, and Portfolio Makers, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Good Fellowship Club (Machine Manufacturer), 1938-1940 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Company Unions, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Company Unions, 1938-1942 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Company Unions, 1939-1940 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Upholsterers, 1935-1938 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Upholsterers, 1937-1938 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, MD, IL, VA, 1936-1938 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Upholsterers, CA, 1938-1939 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, CA, CT, MO, PA, 1938-1939 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, NY, CA, 1937-1939 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, WA, MO, IN, 1938-1939 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, MN, 1938-1939 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, PA, 1939 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, MI, MO, OH, 1939-1941 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, IL, MO, MA, 1938-1940 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, IL, 1939-1940 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, WI, IL, 1937-1940 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, NJ, MO, 1939-1940 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, OH, 1939-1940 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Upholsterers, 1939-1940 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, CA, MO, NY, 1939-1940 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, WI, OH, MO, WA, MI, OR, NJ, 1938-1940 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Upholsterers, AFL, MN, NY, IL, MO, NJ, 1936-1940 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Wire Weavers, OH, 1938-1939 (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - Aluminum Workers, AFL, OH, CT, 1938-1940 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Bait and Tackle Manufacturing, 1937-1939 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Metal and Furniture Manufacturing, 1936-1939 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Metal and Furniture Manufacturing, 1935-1939 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1940, Metal and Furniture Manufacturing, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1942, Metal and Furniture Manufacturing, 1937-1942 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1941, Metal and Furniture Manufacturing, 1939-1941 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1943, Metal and Furniture Manufacturing, 1939-1943 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1944, Metal and Furniture Manufacturing, 1943-1944 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1945, Metal and Furniture Manufacturing, 1942-1945 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers, CIO, 1937-1944 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders and Helpers, AFL, 1938-1944 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Die Sinkers, 1941-1945 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Die Casting Workers, CIO, 1940-1942 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, CIO, 1938-1941 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, CIO, 1937-1942 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, CIO, 1940-1945 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, CIO, 1943-1944 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Electrical Workers, AFL, 1939-1942 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Electrical Workers, AFL, 1941-1944 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Workers, AFL, 1941-1944 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, CIO, 1942-1946 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Electrical Workers, AFL, 1937-1945 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Farm Equipment Workers, CIO, 1941-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Engineers and Operators, AFL, metal and Furniture Manufacturing, 1940-1945 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Furniture Workers, CIO, 1938-1942 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Furniture Workers, CIO, 1941-1943 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Furniture Workers, CIO, 1943-1944 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Furniture Workers, CIO, 1942-1945 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Furniture Workers, CIO, 1938-1945 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Jewelry Workers, AFL, 1939-1945 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Machinists, AFL, 1940-1941 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Machinists, AFL, 1941-1942 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Machinists, AFL, 1941-1942 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Machinists, AFL, 1941-1943 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Machinists, AFL, 1942-1943 (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Machinists, AFL, 1942-1944 (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Machinists, AFL, 1943-1944 (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Machinists, AFL, 1942-1944 (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Machinists, AFL, Metal Manufacturing, 1942-1945 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Marine and Shipbuilding Workers, CIO, 1941-1945 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, AFL, Food Manufacturing, 1940-1943 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Mechanics, 1941-1945 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers, and Helpers, AFL, 1937-1944 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Metal Trades Council, AFL, 1941-1945 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, CIO, Metal Manufacturing, 1940-1945 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Molders, AFL, 1938-1941 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Molders and Foundry Workers, AFL, 1941-1944 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Molders and Foundry Workers, AFL, 1943-1944 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Molders and Foundry Workers, AFL, 1944-1945 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Molders and Foundry Workers, AFL, 1941-1944 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Pattern Makers, AFL, 1941-1944 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Sheet Metal Workers, 1941-1945 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, CIO, 1940-1942 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, CIO, 1941-1942 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, CIO, 1941-1942 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee, CIO, 1942-1943 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - United Steelworkers, CIO, 1942-1943 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - United Steelworkers, CIO, 1943-1944 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - United Steelworkers, CIO, 1942-1944 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - United Steelworkers, 1944-1945 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Stove Mounters, 1940-1944 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Upholsterers' International Union of North America, AFL, 1939-1945 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - American Wire Weavers' Protective Association, AFL, 1941-1942 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Machinery, Metal, Electronics, and Furniture Manufacturing, 1934-1941 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Machinery and Metal Manufacturing, 1933-1940 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Manufacturing Transportation Related Goods, 1938-1943 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Tool and Die Craftsmen, 1941-1943 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Defense/Arms Manufacturing, 1941-1943 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Manufacturing, 1937-1943 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Hand Tools and Bearings Manufacturing, 1941-1943 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Steel Manufacturing, 1941-1944 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Machinery and Metal Manufacturing, 1940-1944 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Manufacturing Transportation Related Goods, 1940-1945 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Machinery, Metal, and Furniture Manufacturing, 1941-1945 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Wartime Production (War Materials), 1943-1945 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Belridge Oil Company - Crude Oil, 1944 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Metal Manufacturing, 1938-1944 (Box 129, Folder 28)
- Series VIII: Industry Code #42, Wholesalers
  - Federal Local Unions (wholesale), 1935 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    Independent Wholesale Grocers Warehouse Employees
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (wholesale), 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Local Industrial Unions, CIO (wholesale), 1937-1939 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Machinists (wholesale), 1936-1940 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - United Mine Workers (wholesale), 1938-1940 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Wholesale, 1936-1939 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1940, Wholesale, 1939-1940 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1942, Wholesale, 1937-1942 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1941, Wholesale, 1938-1941 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Federal Labor Unions, 1944, Wholesale, 1943-1944 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, AFL, Wholesale, 1940-1941 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Oil Distribution, 1943-1944 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Optical Companies, 1941-1944 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Wholesale, 1942-1944 (Box 129, Folder 20)
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail
  - Retail Clerks Association, CA-ID, 1932-1936 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Retail Clerks' International Protective Association, Local 47, 1932-1932; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1932 and expires on 12/31/1932. Covers an unknown number of workers in Oakland, CA
      Format: Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA).
    - Item 2: Perrymans Grocery and Retail Grocery Clerks Union, Local 870, AFL, 1935-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1935 and expires on 10/4/1936. Covers 170 workers in Oakland, CA
    - Item 3: Retail Clerks' International Association, Local 639, AFL, 1935-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1935 and expires on 1/1/1936. Covers an unknown number of workers in Washington, DC
    - Item 4: Retail Clerks' International Association, Local 47, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 1/2/1936 and expires on 1/2/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in Oakland, CA
    - Item 5: Retail Clerks Association, CA-ID, 1932-1936 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Item 6: The Hatterie and Retail Clerks' International Protective Association, Local 860, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers.
    - Item 7: Joe Alpert, Acacia Flower Shop, 6th Ave Flower Shop, Billy Vaus Marrat, Louie Greenwald and Retail Clerks' Protective Association, Local 7, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers 11 workers in Denver, CO
    - Item 8: Retail Shoe and Textile Salesmen's Association, Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 410, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 9: Sanders, Inc., Fargo Wilson Wells Company, Block's Inc., and others and Retail Clerks' International Protective Association, Local 560, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1936 and expires on 9/1/1937. Covers 40 workers in Pocatello, ID
    - Item 10: Sutter Drug Company and Pharmacists Union of Retail Clerks' International Protective Association, Local 838, AFL, 1935-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 12/19/1935 and expires on 12/20/1936. Covers 44 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 11: Lucky Stores, Fairfax Market, D.L. Liquor Stores and others and Retail Food Clerks Union of Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 870, AFL, 1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936. Covers 210 workers in Oakland, CA
    - Item 12: Harts Department Store, Peninsula Stores Ltd., Bettencourt's Grocery, and others and Retail Clerks Union of the Retail Clerks International Protective Association, Local 428, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 2/28/1936 and expires on 2/28/1937. Covers 409 workers in San Jose, CA
    - Item 13: Retail Clerks' International Protective Association, Local 905, AFL, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 130, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 1/1/1937. Covers 500 workers in San Pedro, CA
  - Retail Clerks Association, IL-MT, 1936-1937 (Box 130, Folder 2)